>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 让我们来谈谈这类课程的最后练习。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So let's talk about
this final exercise on classes.
记住，我们把这个名字空间物体变成了一个类。
Remember, we were turning this
name space object into a class.
这些方法中的大部分机制都是一模一样的
Most of the mechanisms inside of these
methods are gonna be exactly the same,
这才是好消息
which is the good news.
你不用修改里面的很多代码但是
You didn't have to change a lot
of the code inside of it, but
我们本质上改变了它的组织结构
we're essentially changing
the organization around it.
所以不要有一个物体能容纳这些东西
So rather than having an object
that holds these things,
我们要去上课了我们要去上课了
we're gonna have a class, and
we're gonna call that class Workshop.
而不是拥有它的属性
And instead of having properties on it,
我们得有个构造函数来设置这些
we're gonna have to have
a constructor that sets those up.
所以我们会制作一个构造函数
So we'll make a constructor that says
this.currentEnrollment 等于空数组和
this.currentEnrollment equals
the empty array and
this.studentRecords 等于空数组。
this.studentRecords equals
the empty array.
现在所有这些都只是我们的分类定义中的方法
Now all the rest of these are just methods
now inside of our class definition so
我们可以去掉这些逗号
we can remove those commas.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 好的，所有这些都应该在没有变化的情况下
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: All right, so all of
those should stand without any changes
因为他们都在处理我们这个例子的这个背景。
because they are all properly handling
this context of our instance.
但有一点我想说的是
But there was one little thing
with the Readme mention,
就是把那些不知道的功能拿出来，
which was to pull out the functions
that are not this aware, and
其中有两个， sortByName 和 printRecord。
there are two of them,
the sortByName and the printRecord.
这两个不是， >> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 这个知道，
These two are not,
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: This aware,
他们并不是特别与讲习班相关的。
and they're not really related
to the Workshop specifically.
所以我们要把他们放在 Helpers 的家长课上
And so we're gonna put them
in a Helpers parent class.
该 Helpers 父类不需要构造函数。
That Helpers parent class
doesn't need a constructor.
但现在我们定义了一个家长阶级，这意味着一个细微的细微差别，
But now that we're defining a parent
class, it does mean a little nuance, which
我们得确保能从我们的孩子构造函数中调用超级函数
is that we're gonna have to make sure to
call super from our child constructor.
如果未定义子构造函数，那么它会自动执行。
If you don't define a child constructor,
it automatically does.
但如果你做一个孩子的构造函数你得叫超级
But if you make a child constructor,
you have to call super
要调用父构造函数，并且必须首先执行此操作。
to invoke the parent constructor,
and you have to do it first.
因此，有一个已为您构建的对象。
So that there is a this object
that has been constructed for you.
好，现在我们需要添加扩展子句，扩展 Helpers。
Okay, so now we need to add
the extends clause, extends Helpers.
然后我们唯一能改变的
And then the only other
change that we should have
我们要把它的深度
to make is that we need
to instantiate the deepJS
通过调用 deepJS 等于新研讨会的对象。
object by calling deepJS
equals new Workshop.
如果我没有错过一些东西，我希望这个代码应该能起作用。
And if I didn't miss something,
hopefully this code should now work.
让我们切换到这个环境，让我们运行这个代码，看看我们得到了什么。
Let's switch over to this environments and
let's run this code and see what we got.
还有我们的产量
And there's our output.
>> Kyle Simpson: 因此我们有基于类的定义，而不是使用
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So there's our
class-based definition rather than using
名称空间。
a name space.
这是我们的讲习班管理的基于类的定义。
It's our class-based definition for
our Workshop management.
有关使用类语法来组织此代码的问题 ?
Questions about using the class
syntax to organize this code?
>> 演讲者 2: 当您从 " 研讨会" 创建深度 JS 时，您是否使用了新的内容 ?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Did you use new when
you created deepJS from Workshop?
>> Kyle Simpson: 是的，我们在处理一个构造函数时要使用新的。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Yep, and we have to use
new when we're dealing with a constructor.
例如，定义 " 研讨会 " 是一个模块工厂时，
For example,
when define Workshop was a module factory,
那只是一个正常的功能所以我们才叫它
that's just a regular function so
we just called it.
但既然这是一个阶级构造函数
But since this is a class constructor,
我们实际上需要用一个新的关键词来引用它，比如你会是一个普通的阶级。
we actually need to invoke it with a new
keyword like you would a normal class.